const STORE = [
    { 
        question: "In jQuery, which of the following is a method to get the value of an attribute for the first element?",
        choice: ['.attr()','.find()','.set()','.search()'],
        answer: '.attr()'
    },

    {
        question: "In jQuery, which method binds an event handler to the click JavaScript event?",
        choice: ['.press()','.click()','.each()','.clicked()'],
        answer: '.click()'
    },
    {
        question: "In jQuery, during the event bubbling phase, what method do we use to select what element the user is interacting with?",
        choice: ['event.user()','event.currentUser()','event.currentTarget()','event.selector()'],
        answer: 'event.currentTarget()'
    },
    {
        question: "In jQuery, we use the method ____ to insert content, specified by a parameter, to the end of each element in the set of matched elements.",
        choice: ['.find()','.add()','.addContent()','.append()'],
        answer: '.append()'
    },
    {
        question: "In jQuery, we use the method ____ to get the first element that matches the selector by testing the element itself and traversing up through its ancestors in the DOM tree. ",
        choice: ['.traverse()','.up()','.closest()','.parent()'],
        answer: '.closest()'
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, how can we remove the final item of an array and return the discarded item?",
        choice: ['.pop()','.remove()','.final()','.end()'],
        answer: '.pop()'
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, what method generates a new array of items by applying the same function to each item in the original array?",
        choice: ['.filter()','.reduce()','.map()','.forEach()'],
        answer: '.map()'
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, what function would we use to aggregate an array data that iterates over the array and maintains the accumulation object?",
        choice: ['.filter()','.aggregate()','.reduce()','.accumulate()'],
        answer: '.reduce()'
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, if we want to remove and return the first item of an array, what method would we use?",
        choice: ['.pop()','.shift()','.sort()','.slice()'],
        answer: '.shift()'
    },
    {
        question: "In JavaScript, how do we get only the 'keys' of an object into an array?",
        choice: ['Object.keys()','Object.map()','key.object()','keys()'],
        answer: 'Object.keys()'
    },
]
